Guide to the Thomas E. Packer Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Inventory, 1833-1864; 0.5; (1 box)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Warren, Ludden & Sollace to Thomas Packer, 1857 August 14, 17 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - A.E. Harmon to Thomas Packer, 1857 August 18 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1857 August 20 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Warren, Ludden & Sollace to Thomas Packer, 1857 August 22 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - A.E. Harmon to Thomas Packer, 1857 August 23 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Warren, Ludden & Sollace to Thomas Packer, 1857 August 26 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1857 August 31, September 7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - J.W. Eddy to Thomas Packer, 1857 September 12 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - R. Goodale to Thomas Packer, 1857 September 21 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1857 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - A.E. Harmon to Thomas Packer, 1857 October 6 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Dawson, Warren & Hyde to Thomas Packer, 1857 October 15 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - William Cathcart to Thomas Packer, 1857 October 23 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Warren, Ludden & Sollace to Thomas Packer, 1857 October 30 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - R. Goodale to Thomas Packer, 1857 November 11 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - A.E. Harmon to Thomas Packer, 1857 November 13 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - R. Goodale to Thomas Packer, 1857 November 27, December 26 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - R. Goodale to Thomas Packer, 1858 January 5 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - A.E. Harmon to Thomas Packer, 1858 January 8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - R. Goodale to Thomas Packer, 1858 February 3 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - A.E. Harmon to Thomas Packer, 1858 February 11 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - J.A. Cotton to Thomas Packer, 1858 April 9, 27, May 18 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - [C. Goodyear?] to [Hisan?] Bradley, 1864 January 24 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Emma J. Packer to Thomas Packer, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Dudley A. Avery to Thomas Packer, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Starr & Co. to Thomas Packer, Undated, n.y. November 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Financial and legal papers, 1833-1860 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1853-1857 (Box 1, Folder 11)